Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Radical Left Publications, 1949-1982; IV.
  - True People's Power (Chicago, IL: People's Press), v. 1 no. 2-5, May-Nov. 1969, 25.
  - USLA Reporter (New York, NY: USLA Justice Committee), v. 2 no. 4-9, Feb. 1968-Fall 1970, 1. (Box 117)
  - United for Peace Reporter (Westbury, NY), v. 1 no. 1-5, March-Aug. 1967, 2.
  - United Irishman = An t Eireannach Aontaithe (Dublin, Ireland), v. 23, no. 6-11, June-Nov. 1969, 3.
  - U. S. Farm News (Hampton, IA: United States Farmers Association), v. 15 no. 5-11, July-Dec. 1,1967; v. 16-30, 1968-1981; v. 31 no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1982, 4.
  - University High School Worrier (Los Angeles, CA), v. 3 no. 2, Nov. 22, 1967, 5.
  - Vanguard (San Francisco, CA), 1 issue, undated, 6.
  - Veterans Stars and Stripes for Peace (Chicago, IL: Veterans for Peace), v. 1 no. 1-8, Sept. 1967-Sept. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-2, Oct. 1968-Jan. 1969, 7.
  - Viet Report (New York, NY), July 1965; Aug., Sept. 1966; April-July 1967; Jan., Summer 1968, 8.
  - Vietnam Digest (Canberra, Australia: "Friends of Vietnam," Australia), no. 4, May 1970, 9.
  - Vietnam G.I. (Chicago, IL), Jan.-Sept. 1968; Jan., June, Aug. 1969; May-Aug. 1970, 10.
  - Vietnam Summer News (Cambridge, MA), v. 1 no. 4, July 21, 1967, 11.
  - View from Here, v. 1 no. 7-17, undated; v. 2 no. 1-21, undated, 12.
  - Viewpoint (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1-2, May/June-Sept./Oct.1977, 13.
  - Vision (Berkeley, CA), v. 1 no. 1, Nov./Dec. 1969, 14.
  - Vocations for Social Change (Canyon, CA), no. 4, Dec. 1968; no. 7-8, May/June-July/Aug. 1969; no. 10-11, Nov/Dec. 1969-Jan./Feb. 1970; no. 26-27, Nov./Dec. 1971-Jan./Feb. 1972, 15.
  - Workforce (Canyon, CA: Vocations for Social Change), no 30, July/Aug. 1972; no. 33, 35, Jan./Feb., May/June 1973; no. 44, 46-47, Jan./Feb., July/Aug-Sept./Oct. 1975; no. 48-49/50, Jan./Feb.-March/April 1976, 16.
  - WRL News (New York, NY: War Register League), Nov.-Dec. 1968; 1969; Jan.-April 1970, 17.
  - Warren Forest Sun (Detroit, MI), no. 4, undated, 18.
  - Washington Peace Center Newsletter (Washington, DC), Jan.-Nov. 1968; Jan.-Feb., April, July-Aug., Nov.-Dec. 1969; April-Dec. 1971; Jan.-July 1972; Feb. 1974; Jan., Dec. 1977, 19.
  - Washington World: A Journal of Political Comment (Washington, DC), v. 6 no. 9, Sept. 1966, 20.
  - West Side Torch (Chicago, IL: West Side Organization), v. 2 no. 24, Aug. 4-18, 1967; v. 3 no. 1-26, Sept. 15, 1967-Sept. 12, 1968; v. 4-5, 1969-1970; v. 6, Jan. 2-March 31, 1971, 1. (Box 118)
  - Western Activism (Kalamazoo, MI: Western Michigan University), v. 3 no. 10, Nov. 16, 1967, 2.
  - Western Socialist (Boston, MA), v. 34 no. 4, 6, 1967; v. 35-38, 1968-1971, 3.
  - Western World Review (Culver City CA: Western World Press), v. 1 no. 1, 3-4, Jan., Fall 1966-Winter 1967; v. 2 no. 3-4, Fall 1967-Winter 1968; v. 3 no. 1-2, Spring-Summer, 1968; v. 4, 1969; v. 5 no. 1, Spring 1970, 4.
  - Westwood Village Square (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-2, Spring-Summer, 1968; v. 2 no. 1, 1st quarter 1969, 5.
  - Wildcat (Chicago, IL: Wildcat Press), v. 1 no. 1-14, 1969-April 1971, 6.
  - Wildcat Report (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1-8, March-Dec. 1969; v. 2, Feb. 1970, 7.
  - Win Magazine (New York, NY: War Resisters League), v. 2 no. 16, Oct. 1966; v. 3 no. 14-21, Aug.-Dec. 1967; v. 4-6, 1968-1970, 8.
  - Winter Soldier (Chicago, IL: Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization), v. 3 no. 9, Nov. 1973; v. 4 no. 1, 3-7, Jan., March-Aug. 1974, 9.
  - Women: A Journal of Liberation (New York, NY), v. 2 no. 1-2, 1970/1971; v. 3 no. 1, 3-4, 1972/1974; v. 4 no. 2-4, 1975/1976; v. 5 no. 1-3, 1976/1977; v. 6 no. 1, 1978, 10.
  - Worcester Punch (Worcester, MA), v. 2 no. 3-4, July-Nov. 1968; v. 3 no. 1-5, Feb.-Dec. 1969; v. 4 no. 1-6, Jan.-May 1970, 1. (Box 119)
  - Worker (London, England), May 1969, 2.
  - Worker (New York, NY: Publishers New Press), v. 32 no. 45-97, June 20-Dec. 1967; v. 33 no. 1-50, Jan.-July 14, 1968, 3.
  - Worker: Publication of a Group of Communist Workers in the 6 Counties., no. 1, undated, 4.
  - Worker and Soldier (New York, NY: Wildcat), no. 1-6, Aug. 1970-Aug. 1971, 5.
  - Worker Esperantist (Ilford (London), England), no. 207, June 5, 1969, 6.
  - Worker Student Bulletin (London, England: Revolutionary Marxist Group), no. 1-4, 1969; Special issue, 1969, 7.
  - Workers Action (Emeryville, CA: Committee for a Labor Party), no. 1, 7-10, July 1968, Nov./Dec. 1970-Sept. 1971, 8.
  - Workers Broadsheet (London, England: London Workers Committee/Working Peoples Party of England), v. 2 no. 9-10, Oct.-Dec. 1967; v. 3 no. 1-4, Jan.-April 1968; v. 4 no. 1-2, June-Sept. 1968; v. 5 no. 1-2, undated, 9.
  - Workers' Power (Baltimore, MD: Workers Party of Maryland), v. 1 no. 1-6, April 17, 1967- Nov. 1968, 10.
  - Workers Press (London, England: Central Committee of the Socialist Labour League), no. 1-40, Sept. 27-Nov. 21, 1969, 11.
  - Workers Vanguard (New York, NY: Spartacist League), no. 1-4, Oct. 1971-Jan. 1972, 1. (Box 120)
  - Workers World (New York, NY), v. 3-11, 1961-1969; v. 12 no. 1-4, Jan.-March 1970, 2.
  - Worklist Mailing (Nashville, TN: Southern Student Organizing Committee), April 5, May 15, 1968, 3.
  - World Balance (Tempe, AZ), v. 1 no. 5, Jan. 29, 1969, 4.
  - World Magazine (New York, NY), Nov. 15, 1969, 5.
  - World Revolution: a Quarterly of World Marxist Leninist Struggle and Thought (New York, NY: Progressive Labor Party), v. 1 no. 1-4, Winter 1967-Oct./Dec. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-3, Jan. 1969-Jan. 1970, 6.
  - York Vietnam Group Report (York, England), no. 30, Feb. 7, 1969, 7.
  - Young Socialist (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1-12, Oct. 1957-Sept. 1958; v. 2 no. 2-10, Nov. 1958-Aug. 1959; v. 3-6, 1959/1960-1962/1963; v. 7 no. 1-4, Dec. 1963-May 1964; v. 8 no. 1-5, Oct. 1964-Aug. 1965; v. 9 no. 1-6, Sept. 1965-Sept. 1966; v. 10, no. 1-7, Oct. 1966-Sept. 1967; v. 11 no. 1, Oct. 1967, 8.
  - Young Socialist Forum (Ottawa, Que.), v. 3 no. 5-6, Sept.-Dec. 1966; v. 4-5, 1967-1968; v. 6 no. 2-9, March-Dec. 1969; v. 7 no. 1, Jan. 1970, 9.
  - Young Worker (Cork, Ireland: Cork Young Socialists), no. 1-3, Dec. 1968-June 1969, 10.
  - Young Worker (New York, NY: Young Workers League), v. 1 no. 1-2, Oct.-Nov. 1967, 11.
  - Youth Action News (Alexandria, VA), v. 1 no. 3, Nov. 1972, 12.
  - Zenarchy (Tampa, FL: Kerry Thornley), Aug.-Dec. 1968, 13.
  - Zimbabwe News (Lusaka, Zambia), v. 2 no. 7, April 13, 1968, 14.
- Pamphlets, 1946-1982; V.
  This series consists of pamphlets published by political, economic, social and religious groups from both the far right and the far left. Pamphlets are arranged alphabetically by publisher, with one folder of pamphlets that were self-published by the author at the end.
  - Action Patriots, 1. (Box 121)
  - Adventures in Thinking, 2.
  - Alert Americans Association, 3.
  - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, 4.
  - American Conservative Union, 5.
  - American Council for Judaism, 6.
  - American Eagle, 7.
  - American Eugenics, 8.
  - American Friends Service Committee, 9.
  - American Jewish Committee, 10.
  - American Jewish Congress, 11.
  - American Legion, 12.
  - American Opinion, 13.
  - American Patriot, 14.
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, 15.
  - America's Future, 16.
  - Anarchos, 17.
  - Anti-Communist International, 18.
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 19.
  - Aquila, 20.
  - Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, 21.
  - Athanasius Press, 22.
  - Australian League of Rights, 23.
  - Bible Pathways, 24.
  - Bible Presbyterian Church, 25.
  - Bible Science Association, 26.
  - Bible Truth Depot, 27.
  - Black and Red, 28.
  - Black Liberation Commission of the Progressive Labor Party, 29.
  - Boniface Press, 30.
  - Bookmailer, 31.
  - Brethren Missionary Herald, 32.
  - British Israel Association of Greater Vancouver, 33.
  - Britons, 33.
  - Campus, 34.
  - Canadian Intelligence, 35.
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, 36.
  - Catholic Traditionalist Movement, 37.
  - Center for Applied Science, 38.
  - Chinese Information Service, 39.
  - Christ for the Nations, 40.
  - Christian Beacon, 41.
  - Christian Book Club of America, 42.
  - Christian Crusade, 43.
  - Christian Educational Association, 44.
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade, 45.
  - Church League of America, 46.
  - Cinema Educational Guild, 1. (Box 122)
  - Circuit Rider, 2.
  - Columbia, 3.
  - Columbia University Forum, 4.
  - Committee for a Free China, 5.
  - Committee for a Free Cuba, 6.
  - Committee for Political Studies, 7.
  - Committee of Christian Laymen of Pittsburgh, 8.
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers, 9.
  - Committee on Pan-American Policy, 10.
  - Communist Party U.S.A., 11.
  - Congressional Quarterly, 12.
  - Connolly Books, 13.
  - Conservative Baptist Association of America, 14.
  - Conservative Baptist Fellowship, 15.
  - Conservative Society of America, 16.
  - Conservative Viewpoint, 17.
  - Constitutional Alliance, 18.
  - Council for Statehood, 19.
  - Council for the Liberation of Daily Life, 20.
  - Defenders of the Christian Faith, 21.
  - Destiny, 22.
  - Diane Books, 23.
  - Don Bell Reports, 24.
  - Economists' National Committee on Monetary Policy, 25.
  - Encounter, 26.
  - End the Draft, 27.
  - Ensign, 28.
  - Esco, 29.
  - Faith Theological Seminary, 30.
  - Fathers of the Oratory of Kentucky, 31.
  - Federated Libraries, 32.
  - Florida Coalition of Patriotic Societies, 33.
  - Flute, 34.
  - Foreign Language Press, 35.
  - Forum, 36.
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 37.
  - Free Economy Association, 38.
  - Free Pacific Association, 39.
  - Free Society Association, 40.
  - Freedom Enterprises, 41.
  - Freedom Socialist, 42.
  - Friends Book Club, 43.
  - Friendship Press, 44.
  - Greater Nebraskan, 45.
  - Guardian, 46.
  - Hawaii Foundation for Economic Freedoms, 1. (Box 123)
  - Headlines, 2.
  - Heads Up, 3.
  - Helmet and Sword, 4.
  - Herald of Freedom, 5.
  - Independent Socialist Committee, 6.
  - Indochina Research Center, 7.
  - Institute for American Democracy, 8.
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 9.
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 10.
  - International Association of Cancer Victims and Friends, 11.
  - International Peace and Security Program, 12.
  - Interpreter, 13.
  - Irish Communist Organisation, 14.
  - Iskcon Books, 15.
  - Jet, 16.
  - John Birch Society, 17.
  - Kansas University Student Rights Coordinating Committee, 18.
  - Kimtex Corporation, 19.
  - KIPCO, 20.
  - La Jolla Rancho Press, 21.
  - Laymen's Commission of the American Council of Christian Churches, 22.
  - Liberty Lobby, 23.
  - Literature and Ideology, 24.
  - Long House, 25.
  - Lutheran Free Conference, 26.
  - Lutheran Laymen's League, 27.
  - Marxist-Leninist Organisation of Britain, 28.
  - Mayday Collective, 29.
  - Merit, 30.
  - Mertmont, 31.
  - Methodist Panel, 32.
  - Missouri Synod (Lutheran), 33.
  - Modern Age, 34.
  - Modern Utopian, 35.
  - National Christian Association, 1. (Box 124)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee, 2.
  - National Conference of Friends on Race Relations, 3.
  - National Congress of Racial Equality, 4.
  - National Defense Committee, 5.
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 6.
  - National Party of America, 7.
  - National Review, 8.
  - National States Rights Party, 9.
  - Native Sons of Canada, 10.
  - New Century, 11.
  - News and Letter, 12.
  - Noontide Press, 13.
  - North American Congress on Latin America, 14.
  - Norwegian Synod of the American Evangelical Lutheran Church, 15.
  - Oberlin College, 16.
  - Ohio Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends, 17.
  - Old Fashioned Prophecy Magazine, 18.
  - Omni, 19.
  - Our Generation, 20.
  - Pacific Studies Center, 21.
  - Palestine Arab Delegation, 22.
  - Palestine Liberation Organization, 23.
  - Patrick Henry Press, 24.
  - Patriotic Research Bureau, 25.
  - Pendle Hill, 26.
  - Pine Tree Press, 27.
  - Pioneer, 28.
  - Polaroid Revolutionary Workers Movement, 29.
  - Prophetic Herald, 30.
  - Provincial Press, 31.
  - Quail Books, 32.
  - Radio Church of God, 33.
  - Rampart Journal, 34.
  - Ray O. Light, 35.
  - Reader's Digest, 36.
  - Regular Baptist Press, 37.
  - Revolutionary Marxist Tendency of the Fourth International, 38.
  - Right Cause, 39.
  - Russell Press, 40.
  - Sam Adams Committee of Public Safety, 41.
  - San Diego Catholics for Better Libraries, 42.
  - Soldiers of the Cross, 43.
  - Solidarity, 44.
  - Sons of Liberty, 45.
  - Soulbook, 46.
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 47.
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 48.
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 49.
  - Tarrant County (Texas) Public Affairs Forum, 1. (Box 125)
  - Taxpayers Educational Association, 2.
  - Temple of Understanding, 3.
  - Through to Victory, 4.
  - Thunderbolt, 5.
  - Trinity Book Room, 6.
  - Trumpet, 7.
  - Truth Forum, 8.
  - Twentieth Century Reformation Hour, 9.
  - Umbra, 10.
  - Una Voce, 11.
  - Unicorn Press, 12.
  - United Lutheran Church in America, 13.
  - United Nations, 14.
  - United States Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, 15.
  - United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities, 16.
  - United States Flag Committee, 17.
  - Universal Challenger, 18.
  - U.S.A., 19.
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 20.
  - Victory Press, 21.
  - Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government, 22.
  - Voice of Americanism, 23.
  - Western Baptist Bible College, 24.
  - Wilmington College, 25.
  - Winrod, 26.
  - Wisconsin Lutheran Seminary, 27.
  - Women for Constitutional Government, 28.
  - World Anti-Communist League. China Chapter, 29.
  - World Prophetic Ministry, 30.
  - World View, 31.
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 32.
  - Young Socialist, 33.
  - Youth Action, 34.
  - Youth for Stalin, 35.
  - Author-Published Pamphlets, 36.
- Organizations and Individuals, 1946-1982; VI.
  This series consists of assorted materials by and about political, economic, social and religious groups from both the far right and the far left. Folders are arranged alphabetically by the name of the organization or individual.
  - Ad Hoc Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Party, U.S.A., 1. (Box 126)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Defense of Life, 2.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Middle East, 3.
  - Advocates of Our Lady, 4.
  - Aladextra Press, 5.
  - Alcorn, Margaret, 6.
  - Alerted Americans Association, 7.
  - Alerted Americans (Pa.), 8.
  - All Slavic Publishing House, 9.
  - Alliance for Abandoned American Fighting Men, 10.
  - Allegheny Council on Civil Rights, 11.
  - Allen, Marilyn, 12.
  - Alternatives! Foundation, 13.
  - American-African Affairs Committee, 14.
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 15.
  - American Association of University Professors, 16.
  - American Capsule News, 17.
  - American Challenge, 18.
  - American Christian Freedom Society, 19.
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 20.
  - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, 21.
  - American Conservative Union, 22.
  - American Council of Christian Churches, 23.
  - American Council of Judaism, 24.
  - American Documentary Films, 25.
  - American Economic Foundation, 26.
  - American Education Lobby, 27.
  - American Emergency Committee in the Panama Canal, 28.
  - American Eugenics Party, 29.
  - American Flag Association, 30.
  - American Flag Committee, 31.
  - American Friends of Russian Freedom, 32.
  - American Friends Service Committee, 33.
  - American Hungarian Committee, 34.
  - American Independent Movement, 35.
  - American Institute for Political Communication, 36.
  - American Jewish Association, 37.
  - American Jewish Committee, 38.
  - American Lobby, 39.
  - American Mercury, 40.
  - American Nazi Party, 41.
  - American Open Library Books, 42.
  - American Opinion, 43.
  - American Party of Georgia, 44.
  - American Patriot, 45.
  - American Security Council, 46.
  - American-Southern Africa Council, 47.
  - American Tract Society, 48.
  - Americanism Educational League, 49.
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, 50.
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 51.
  - Americans for Indian Opportunity, 52.
  - Americans for Law and Order, 53.
  - Americans for National Security, 54.
  - Americans United, 55.
  - America's Future, 56.
  - Amnesty International, 57.
  - Anarchos, 58.
  - Anglican Orthodox Church of North America, 59.
  - Anglo-Saxon Federation of America, 60.
  - Anti-Communist Confederation of Polish Freedom Fighters, 61.
  - Anti-Communist International, 62.
  - Aquila Press, 63.
  - Arizonans for Mental Freedom, 64.
  - Armed Forces Roll Call Newsletter, 65.
  - Artists' Workshop Press, 66.
  - Asian People's Anti-Communist League, 67.
  - Asian Speakers Bureau, 68.
  - Assembly of Captive European Nations, 69.
  - Associated Gospel Churches, 70.
  - Association for Christian Schools, 71.
  - Association for Social Psychology, 72.
  - Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, 73.
  - Association of the Covenant People, 74.
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, 75.
  - Ave Maria Press, 76.
  - Awake America for Christ, 77.
  - Baltimore Defense Committee, 1. (Box 127)
  - Baltimore Peace Action Center, 2.
  - Bay Area Revolutionary Union, 3.
  - Benjamin Franklin Center, 4.
  - Bernard for Senate Committee, 5.
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation, 6.
  - Better Books, 7.
  - Bible Protestant Mission, 8.
  - Bible Science Association, 9.
  - Biblical Evangelism, 10.
  - Birmingham Independent, 11.
  - Black and Red, 12.
  - Black Mask, 13.
  - Black Theatre, 14.
  - Blanco, Hugo, 15.
  - Blessing, William L., 16.
  - Blue Army of Fatima, 17.
  - Bond, 18.
  - Boniface Press, 19.
  - Bookmailer, 20.
  - Books for Libertarians, 21.
  - Breakthrough, 22.
  - British Israel Association of Greater Vancouver, 23.
  - British Israel World Federation, 24.
  - Buckley, James L., 25.
  - Bulletin Board of the Conservatives, 26.
  - CADRE (Chicago Area Draft Resistance), 27.
  - California Conservatives, 28.
  - California Statesman, 29.
  - Canadian Council of Evangelical Protestant Churches, 30.
  - Canadian League of Rights, 31.
  - Canadian Peace Research Institute, 32.
  - Capsule News, 33.
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, 34.
  - Catholic Fact Research Association, 35.
  - Catholic Traditionalist Movement, 36.
  - Catholic Worker, 37.
  - Catholics United for the Faith, 38.
  - Caxton Printers, 39.
  - CBC Radio Canada, 40.
  - CEASE, 41.
  - Cedarville College, 42.
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 43.
  - Central Baptist Church Publications, 44.
  - Century Press, 45.
  - Charles Hallberg & Co., 46.
  - Chedney Press, 47.
  - Chinese Information Service, 48.
  - Christ and Country Books, 49.
  - Christ for the Nations, 50.
  - Christian Amendment Movement, 51.
  - Christian Anti-Communist Crusade, 52.
  - Christian Beacon, 53.
  - Christian Book Club of America, 54.
  - Christian Crusade, 55.
  - Christian Educational Association, 56.
  - Christian Freedom Foundation, 57.
  - Christian Life, 58.
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade, 59.
  - Christian Patriot, 60.
  - Christian Research, 61.
  - Christianity Today, 62.
  - Christians Awake, 63.
  - Christ's Mission, 64.
  - Church League of America, 65.
  - Church Times, 66.
  - Cinema Educational Guild, 1. (Box 128)
  - Circuit Rider, 2.
  - Citizens Against Legalized Murder, 3.
  - Citizens Commission Against Crime, 4.
  - Citizens Committee for a Free Cuba, 5.
  - Citizens Concerned for the Democratic Process, 6.
  - Citizens Councils of America, 7.
  - Citizens for Decent Literature, 8.
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 9.
  - Citizens of Michigan for Constitutional Government Committee, 10.
  - Citizens to End White Racism, 11.
  - Citizens' Report, 12.
  - Civil Liberties Legal Defense Fund, 13.
  - Clark, Joseph, 14.
  - Clergymen and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam, 15.
  - Clergymen's Committee on China, 16.
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 17.
  - Cold War Council, 18.
  - Columbus Urban League Education Committee, 19.
  - Combat, 20.
  - Committee for a Free China, 21.
  - Committee for Freedom of Choice in Education, 22.
  - Committee of Christian Laymen, 23.
  - Committee of One Million, 24.
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers, 25.
  - Committee of Russian Slaves of Jewish Communism, 26.
  - Committee of the States, 27.
  - Committee on Pan-American Policy, 28.
  - Committee on Un-American Activities, 29.
  - Committee to Aid the Bloomington Students, 30.
  - Committee to Re-Elect Senator Clark, 31.
  - Committee to Restore Lithuanian Independence, 32.
  - Committee to Restore the Constitution, 33.
  - Committee to Support Middle East Liberation, 34.
  - Commonweal Associates, 35.
  - Communist Party of the USA, 36.
  - Communist Party of Western Pennsylvania, 37.
  - Community Development Conference, 38.
  - Community for New Politics, 39.
  - Concern, 40.
  - Concerned Presbyterians, 41.
  - Concordia Historical Institute, 42.
  - Confessional Lutheran, 43.
  - Congregational Christian Historical Society, 44.
  - Congregational Methodist Church, 45.
  - Congress of Freedom, 46.
  - Congressional Quarterly, 47.
  - Conservative Baptist Association of America, 48.
  - Conservative Book Club, 49.
  - Conservative Caucus, 50.
  - Conservative Society of America, 51.
  - Conservative Viewpoint, 52.
  - Conservatives for Nixon, 53.
  - Constitution Party, 54.
  - Constitutional Alliance, 55.
  - Constitutional Party, 56.
  - Constructive Action, 57.
  - Consumers Party of Philadelphia, 58.
  - Conversion Center, 59.
  - Cook, Ben, 60.
  - CORE, 61.
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 62.
  - Council for the Liberation of Daily Life, 63.
  - Council for a Livable World, 64.
  - Council for Statehood, 65.
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs, 66.
  - Councilor, 67.
  - Count Down, 68.
  - Courtney, Kent, 69.
  - Cow Country Commentary, 70.
  - Craig Press, 71.
  - Creation Research Society, 72.
  - Creation Science Research Center, 73.
  - Crestwood Books, 74.
  - Cuban Revolutionary Unity Movement, 75.
  - Daily World, 1. (Box 129)
  - Dan Smoot Report, 2.
  - Dart, 3.
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Defense Committee, 4.
  - Defenders of the American Constitution, 5.
  - Defenders of the Christian Faith, 6.
  - Defenders of the U.S.A. Republic, 7.
  - Democratic Liberation Party, 8.
  - Destiny Publishers, 9.
  - Dickinson, William L., 10.
  - Dissent, 11.
  - Divine Word Seminary, 12.
  - Dolphin Press, 13.
  - Dorrity, Thomas G., 14.
  - Draft Resistance Clearing House, 15.
  - Dustbooks, 16.
  - Eagle Forum, 17.
  - Eagle Trust Fund, 18.
  - East Asian Research Institute, 19.
  - East End Education Committee, 20.
  - Education Information, 21.
  - Emergency Appeal for Czech Refugees, 22.
  - Emergency Committee Against Forced Housing, 23.
  - Ethridge, Tom, 24.
  - Eugene Bradley Defense Fund, 25.
  - Evangelical Challenge, 26.
  - Evangelical Methodist Church, 27.
  - Evangelical Methodists, 28.
  - Exposé, 29.
  - Facts in Education, 30.
  - Faith and Freedom Center, 31.
  - Farmers Liberty League, 32.
  - Fathers of Saint Edmund, 33.
  - Federation of American Citizens of German Descent, 34.
  - Feliciano, Carlos, 35.
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 36.
  - Forum Publishing Co., 37.
  - Foundation for American Christian Education, 38.
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 39.
  - Foundation Truth Magazine, 40.
  - 14th Ward Democratic Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 41.
  - Free China Weekly, 42.
  - Free Cuba Radio, 43.
  - Free Economy Association, 44.
  - Free Pacific Association, 45.
  - Free School of New York, 46.
  - Free Society Association, 47.
  - Freedom Academy, 48.
  - Freedom Center (Portland, Ore.), 49.
  - Freedom Foundation, 50.
  - Freedom Magazine, 51.